Jonah Sherman Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Ephemera, 1874 - 1945; 6; Boxes: 85 - 121
  - Subseries 6.1: Advertising and Postcard Collection, 1874 - 1945; 6.1; Boxes: 85
    - Subseries 6.1.2: Postcards, 1904 - 2002; 6.1.2; Boxes: 85 - 87
      - Houses and Buildings - Clinton House, 1906 - 1908 (Folder 6, Box 86)
      - Houses and Buildings - Court House, 1907 - 1925 (Folder 7, Box 86)
      - Houses and Buildings - Miscellany, 1909 - 1965 (Folder 8, Box 86)
      - Libraries, 1916 (Folder 9, Box 86)
      - Parks and Recreation, 1908 - 1945 (Folder 10, Box 86)
      - Politics, circa 1908 (Folder 11, Box 86)
      - Post Offices, 1907 - 1911 (Folder 12, Box 86)
      - Poughkeepsie - General, 1907 - 1918 (Folder 13, Box 86)
      - Religion - Churches, 1905 - 1930 (Folder 14, Box 86)
      - River/Riverfront, 1909 - 1938 (Folder 15, Box 86)
      - Street Scenes - Hooker Ave, circa 1912 (Folder 16, Box 86)
      - Street Scenes - Main Street, 1909 - 1939 (Folder 17, Box 86)
      - Street Scenes - Market Street, 1907 - 1923 (Folder 18, Box 86)
      - Street Scenes - Miscellany, 1908 - 1917 (Folder 19, Box 86)
      - Miscellany, 1904 - 1986 (Folder 20, Box 86)
  - Subseries 6.2: Newspaper advertisements, 6.2; Box: 87
    - Advertisement for Buckeye Premium Mower, undated (Folder 1, Box 87)
    - Advertisement for performance of Uncle Tom's Cabin at the Collingwood Opera House, undated (Folder 2, Box 87)
    - Advertisement for the Progressive Merchants of Poughkeepsie, 1937 (Folder 3, Box 87)
    - Advertisement for the Progressive Merchants of Poughkeepsie, 1937 (Folder 4, Box 87)
    - Advertisement for St. Paul's Lutheran Church's fair and festival, undated (Folder 5, Box 87)
  - Subseries 6.3: Other publications, 1881 - 1938; 6.3; Box: 87
    - $25.00 for a Name - volume 1, number 1; Poughkeepsie, NY, 1902 December 15 (Folder 6, Box 87)
    - Ballou's Pictorial Drawing-Room Companion, undated (Folder 7, Box 87)
    - Carriers' Annual Address of the Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle, 1881 (Folder 8, Box 87)
    - Carriers' Annual Address of the Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle, 1883 (Folder 9, Box 87)
    - Demorest's Monitor of Fashions - volume II, number 3, 1883 (Folder 10, Box 87)
    - Important and Interesting Historical Events, presented by Eastman Business College, undated (Folder 11, Box 87)
    - Metropolitan Fashions - volume XIV, number 4, 1884 (Folder 12, Box 87)
    - Metropolitan Fashions - volume XIV, number 5, 1884 (Folder 13, Box 87)
    - Photo Script, Poughkeepsie, NY, 1938 June (Folder 14, Box 87)
    - The Queen Illustrated Magazine of Fashion - volume VIII, number 1, 1881 (Folder 15, Box 87)
    - The Queen Illustrated Magazine of Fashion - volume X, number 5, 1883 (Folder 16, Box 87)
  - Subseries 6.4: Objects, 6.4; Boxes: 109 - 121
    - No Vacancy sign, undated (Folder 1, Box 88)
    - 25 yard sticks labeled with various Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 88)
    - 5 Boxes from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 3, Box 88)
    - Shopping bag from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 4, Box 88)
    - Box from The Wallace Co., Poughkeepsie's Finest Store, undated (Folder 5, Box 88)
    - The Bank of New York, 200 Year Anniversary Banner, 1984 (Folder 6, Box 88)
    - Pennant from the State convention in Poughkeepsie, NY - Odd Fellows, 1913 (Folder 7, Box 88)
    - Souvenir of Poughkeepsie Pennant, undated (Folder 8, Box 88)
    - Calendar cover from Poughkeepsie Coop. G.L.F. Service Inc., undated (Folder 9, Box 88)
    - Paper Flyer: Luckey, Platt Co. Dry Goods, Carpets, etc., The Cheap Cash Store. 332, 334, 336 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., One Proce to All, Butterick's Patterns [Merry Christmas not scribbled], undated (Folder 10, Box 88)
    - Poughkeepsie High School - Central Hudson Valley Basketball Championship Trophy, 1919 - 1922 (Folder 1, Box 89)
    - Box from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 1, Box 90)
    - Box from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 2, Box 90)
    - Box from M. Shwartz and Company, undated (Folder 3, Box 90)
    - Box from Zimmer Brothers, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 4, Box 90)
    - Cigar box labeled Up to Date, undated (Folder 5, Box 90)
    - Cuban cigar box labeled: Connecting Link, The Poughkeepsie Railroad Bridge, undated (Folder 6, Box 90)
    - Nelson House Gift Shop Box, undated (Folder 7, Box 90)
    - Small box from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 8, Box 90)
    - Small box from Marguerite Ball, 14 Liberty Street, Poughkeepsie NY, undated (Folder 9, Box 90)
    - Small box from Wallace's, undated (Folder 10, Box 90)
    - Small unlabeled red box, undated (Folder 11, Box 90)
    - Standard Gage Company, wooden box, undated (Folder 12, Box 90)
    - Wood box from Perlmutter Furniture Company - contains a number of address cards, undated (Folder 13, Box 90)
    - Wood box from Perlmutter Furniture Company - contains a number of address cards, undated (Folder 14, Box 90)
    - Glass jar lid labeled Walnut Sundae, Kustas Chamberas, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 91)
    - Mug advertising the Bardavon 1869 Opera House, undated (Folder 2, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1926 (Folder 3, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1927 (Folder 4, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1929 (Folder 5, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1935 (Folder 6, Box 91)
    - 1935 (Folder 7, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1943 (Folder 8, Box 91)
    - Ready Reference Diary from Luckey, Platt and Company, 1951 (Folder 9, Box 91)
    - Vase from The Saltford Flower Shop, undated (Folder 10, Box 91)
    - Bottle capping tool with bottle from Star Beverages, Inc., Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 92)
    - 24 lb scale from C.D. Johnson Hardware Company, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 93)
    - Box from Federal Ball Bearings, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 2, Box 93)
    - Jar from Riverside Bank, undated (Folder 1, Box 94)
    - Jar from Sherman Furniture Rentals, undated (Folder 2, Box 95)
    - Metal printing box, undated (Folder 3, Box 94)
    - Reynolds Coffee Tin, undated (Folder 4, Box 94)
    - 3 glass bottles labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 95)
    - Mug from Marist College, undated (Folder 2, Box 95)
    - 4 glass bottles labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 96)
    - 6 glass bottles labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 97)
    - Glass bottle labeled: Bevier Yoakam Druggists, 359 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 2, Box 97)
    - Glass bottle labeled: Doty Humphrey Drug Co. Pharmacists, 394 Main St. near S. Hamilton St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 3, Box 97)
    - Glass bottle labeled: Krieger's Pharmacy, 130 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 4, Box 97)
    - Glass bottle labeled: Elgee Beverage, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 5, Box 97)
    - 10 glass bottles labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 98)
    - Address book form Wyndham Poughkeepsie, undated (Folder 2, Box 98)
    - Glass bottle labeled: Doty Humphrey Drug Co. Pharmacists, 394 Main St. near S. Hamilton St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 3, Box 98)
    - Mirror labeled Harry T. Briggs General Insurance, 2 Cannon Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 4, Box 98)
    - Scissors Sharpener labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 5, Box 9)
    - Test tube in blue box, undated (Folder 6, Box 98)
    - Thimble labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 7, Box 98)
    - 13 Stamps labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 99)
    - Key holder-Dutchess Bank Trust Company, undated (Folder 2, Box 99)
    - Key labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 3, Box 99)
    - Printing plates of Poughkeepsie Eagle building, undated (Folder 4, Box 99)
    - United Way logo, undated (Folder 5, Box 99)
    - 500 lb pulley, undated (Folder 1, Box 100)
    - 500 lb pulley from Lanebro Manufacturing Company, undated (Folder 2, Box 100)
    - 500 lb pulley from Lanebro Manufacturing Company, undated (Folder 3, Box 100)
    - Folder from Robert A. Jankovics Insurance Agency, undated (Folder 4, Box 100)
    - Folding notary stamp, undated (Folder 5, Box 100)
    - Schrauth's Ice Cream box, undated (Folder 6, Box 100)
    - Wallet with cards from local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 7, Box 100)
    - 2 paper Thermometers from Grossman's, undated (Folder 1, Box 101)
    - Thermometer labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 100)
    - 3 calendars labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 3, Box 101)
    - 3 key chains labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 4, Box 101)
    - 7 shoehorns labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 5, Box 101)
    - 10 pocket knives labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 6, Box 101)
    - Assorted Poughkeepsie-related buttons and pins, undated (Folder 7, Box 101)
    - Button from Poughkeepsie Savings Bank, undated (Folder 8, Box 101)
    - Clamp labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 9, Box 101)
    - Forbes Wallace tag, undated (Folder 10, Box 101)
    - Luckey Platt Shoehorn, undated (Folder 11, Box 101)
    - Luckey Platt Thermometer, undated (Folder 12, Box 101)
    - Medals labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 13, Box 101)
    - Metal thermometer labeled with local Poughkeepsie business, undated (Folder 14, Box 101)
    - Mini plate from Amenia, undated (Folder 15, Box 101)
    - Pin: Excelsior Club, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 16, Box 101)
    - Mertal thermometer labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 17, Box 101)
    - Thermometer with photo - Harry T. Briggs General Insurance, 2 Cannon Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1944 (Folder 18, Box 101)
    - Two Pins from Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1886, 1896 (Folder 19, Box 101)
    - Two promotional thermometers: Grossman's, Hudson Valley's Largest Wine and Liquor Store - 541 Main Street, call 885 for rapid delivery, undated (Folder 20, Box 101)
    - Green China Cup - Morgan House, undated (Folder 1, Box 102)
    - Green Oval China Plate - Morgan House, undated (Folder 2, Box 102)
    - Plate from Morgan House, undated (Folder 3, Box 102)
    - 3 bars of soap from Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 103)
    - Central Hudson flashlight, undated (Folder 2, Box 103)
    - Cleaning tissues from Poughkeepsie Savings Bank, undated (Folder 3, Box 103)
    - Cocktail recipes labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 5, Box 103)
    - Coaster from the Dutchess County Bar Association, undated (Folder 4, Box 103)
    - Credit card labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 8, Box 103)
    - Fargo pet rock, undated (Folder 7, Box 103)
    - Flashlight from Marine Midland Bank, undated (Folder 7, Box 103)
    - Glass Teller sign, undated (Folder 9, Box 103)
    - House number: Vassar College 531, undated (Folder 10, Box 103)
    - Jonah Sherman ID card from Dutchess Bank, undated (Folder 11, Box 103)
    - Key book labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 12, Box 103)
    - Notepad from Hotel Campbell, undated (Folder 13, Box 103)
    - Promotional item from Stec Motor Service, undated (Folder 14, Box 103)
    - Rain hat labeled Fleishman's Poughkeepsie NY, undated (Folder 15, Box 103)
    - Rusty Spoon, undated (Folder 16, Box 103)
    - Safe deposit box key in envelope from Farmers Mattewan National bank, undated (Folder 17, Box 103)
    - Bank Books, undated (Folder 1, Box 104)
    - Bank Pouch from Farmers and Manufacturers Bank, undated (Folder 2, Box 104)
    - Bank Pouch from Merchants Bank, undated (Folder 3, Box 104)
    - Check book and check book covers, undated (Folder 4, Box 104)
    - Locking Bank Bag from Bankers Trust Company of Hudson Valley, undated (Folder 5, Box 104)
    - Locking Bank Bag from Barclays Bank, New York, NY, undated (Folder 6, Box 104)
    - Promotional calendars from Poughkeepsie banks, undated (Folder 7, Box 104)
    - Trinket from Poughkeepsie Savings Bank, undated (Folder 8, Box 104)
    - 3 Poughkeepsie trolley tokens, undated (Folder 1, Box 105)
    - 5 pins from Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 (Folder 2, Box 105)
    - 7 Commemorative Pins, undated (Folder 3, Box 105)
    - 10 ribbons from local Civic Organizations, undated (Folder 4, Box 105)
    - 128th Regiment Ribbon, undated (Folder 5, Box 104)
    - Black case from Quintard Bros., undated (Folder 6, Box 105)
    - Cough syrup, prepared for Doty Humphrey Drug Co., Inc., 394 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 7, Box 105)
    - Devon horse show ribbon, center medallion only, 1927 (Folder 8, Box 105)
    - Folder from Van Scoy Jeweler, undated (Folder 9, Box 105)
    - Jewelry box from E. Van Scoy, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 10, Box 105)
    - Jewelry case from De's Jewelers, undated (Folder 11, Box 105)
    - Key to the City of Poughkeepsie pin, undated (Folder 12, Box 105)
    - Lighter, undated (Folder 13, Box 105)
    - Poughkeepsie Railroad Bridge Pin, undated (Folder 14, Box 105)
    - Rusty Key, undated (Folder 15, Box 105)
    - Screw driver labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 16, Box 105)
    - Vassar College pin, undated (Folder 17, Box 105)
    - 31 rulers labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 106)
    - Bag of 16 matchbooks from Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 106)
    - Match Book covers, undated (Folder 3, Box 106)
    - Nelson House Matches, undated (Folder 4, Box 106)
    - Piano roll produced in Poughkeepsie, undated (Folder 5, Box 106)
    - Prudential Insurance Company, Premium Receipt Books, 1910 - 1940 (Folder 6, Box 106)
    - Ruler from Marshall Sterling Insurance, undated (Folder 7, Box 106)
    - Wood block with two coins celebrating Main Mall dedication, 1974 (Folder 8, Box 106)
    - 4 clothes hangers labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 107)
    - 4 flyers for local performances, undated (Folder 2, Box 107)
    - Mechanical aid for Fishing with alarm buzzer - patented by Alertric Company, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 3, Box 107)
    - Paper bag from Barron's, Poughkeepsie, Nanuet, Yonkers, undated (Folder 4, Box 107)
    - Program from Memorial commemorating 6 Poughkeepsie men who dies in World War II, circa 1946 (Folder 5, Box 107)
    - 2 folding wallets labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 108)
    - 2 eye glasses from J. Coleman Moselle, undated (Folder 1, Box 108)
    - 5 eyeglass cases labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 3, Box 108)
    - 8 notepads labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 4, Box 108)
    - G. Dudley, Poughkeepsie NY Dutchess Razor in case s, undated (Folder 5, Box 108)
    - Wood Box: A.W. Triller, Optometrist-Optician, 328 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 6, Box 108)
    - Wood Box: C.H. Perkins, Optical Laboratory, 268 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 7, Box 108)
    - Wood Box: C.H. Perkins, Optical Laboratory, 268 Main St., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., undated (Folder 8, Box 108)
    - Box labeled Wm. C. Bauer, 310 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 9, Box 108)
    - Box labeled Wm. C. Bauer, 310 Main Street, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 10, Box 108)
    - 2 paper fans with fall and winter scences labeled Mid-Hudson Oil., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Phone 8400, undated (Folder 1, Box 109)
    - 2 paper fans labeled NEHI Bottling Company, 45 Belmont Ave. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Phone 420 - advertisement for Royal Crown Cola, undated (Folder 2, Box 109)
    - 3 bottle caps from local Poughkeepsie banks, undated (Folder 3, Box 109)
    - 3 bottle openers labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 4, Box 109)
    - 5 paper fans from Schrauth's Ice Cream, undated (Folder 5, Box 109)
    - 4 Paper fans labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 5, Box 109)
    - DeLaval Notebook, 1925 (Folder 7, Box 109)
    - Dime savings tin from Poughkeepsie YWCA, undated (Folder 8, Box 109)
    - Fly Swatter? labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 9, Box 109)
    - Glass block from A.C. Dutton Lumber Company, undated (Folder 10, Box 109)
    - Nail from Farmers and Manufactures National Banks, undated (Folder 12, Box 109)
    - Napkin from Nelson House, undated (Folder 13, Box 109)
    - Promotional sign: Courtney's Laundry, 26-28 Catharine Street Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Phone 770 - 'We have a service to suit your wants', undated (Folder 13, Box 109)
    - Promotional sign: French Pastry Shop, 368 Main St., undated (Folder 14, Box 109)
    - Assorted caps and advertisements for milk, sour cream and orange ade, undated (Folder 1, Box 110)
    - Bridge and Whist score calculator labeled Walter A. Streb, 11 Market Street, Poughkeepsie N.Y., undated (Folder 2, Box 110)
    - Buttons - Dutchess Manufacturing, undated (Folder 3, Box 110)
    - Card from F.S. Webster and Company, undated (Folder 4, Box 110)
    - Fitchett Bros. Creamed Cottage Cheese container, undated (Folder 5, Box 110)
    - J.D. Johnson Co. Thermometer, undated (Folder 5, Box 110)
    - Keychain with measuring tape labeled Effron Fuel Oil Company, undated (Folder 7, Box 110)
    - Measuring tape labeled Fitchett Brothers, undated (Folder 8, Box 110)
    - Measuring tape from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 9, Box 110)
    - Needle book labeled Chas. W. Swift, 7 Garden Street, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 10, Box 110)
    - Needle books labeled with Fitchett's, undated (Folder 11, Box 110)
    - Picture frame from George C. Knauss, Quality Meats and Poultry, undated (Folder 12, Box 110)
    - Poughkeepsie Police button, undated (Folder 13, Box 110)
    - Vallet Autostrop Razor, undated (Folder 14, Box 110)
    - 4 pencils labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 111)
    - 2 pens labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 111)
    - Ash Tray labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 3, Box 111)
    - Coin bank box from Poughkeepsie Savings Bank, undated (Folder 4, Box 111)
    - Giant Novelty pencil from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 5, Box 111)
    - Mail or note holder from Luckey, Platt and Company, circa 1940 (Folder 6, Box 122)
    - Pledge of Allegiance cards from Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 7, Box 111)
    - Sign - 'Read the Poughkeepsie Eagle', undated (Folder 8, Box 111)
    - 5 Stamps labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 112)
    - 5 pressed seals, undated (Folder 1, Box 112)
    - China Plate with view of Poughkeepsie, written: 'View of Poughkeepsie,' sketched by Archibald Robertson in 1796, shows the east fa'ade of the Dutchess County Court House in which the 65 Delegates of the State of New York Ratified the United States Constitution in 1788. The Dutchess County Horticulture Society salutes the Bicentennial of the Ratification of the Constitution 1788-1988. (Folder 4, Box 108)
    - Tag from Crosley refrigeration unit, undated (Folder 4, Box 112)
    - 2 letter openers labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 113)
    - 3 Pottery Test block, undated (Folder 2, Box 113)
    - 6 Christmas quarter-savings folders from local Poughkeepsie banks, undated (Folder 3, Box 113)
    - Black Notepad labeled Souvenir of Poughkeepsie, undated (Folder 4, Box 113)
    - DeLaval Separator Company plaque, undated (Folder 5, Box 113)
    - EFCO Bakery Mixes - baking tool, undated (Folder 6, Box 113)
    - Handle from Effron's Children's Corner Teen Shop, undated (Folder 5, Box 113)
    - Ice pick labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 8, Box 113)
    - Letter opener from B. B. Lighting Fixture Company, undated (Folder 9, Box 113)
    - Luckey Platt handles with string, undated (Folder 10, Box 113)
    - Mag-Lite, - Solitaire, undated (Folder 11, Box 113)
    - Smith Brothers Cough Drop Box - small, undated (Folder 12, Box 113)
    - Toilet paper roll labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 13, Box 113)
    - 2 Mugs labeled Fargo, undated (Folder 1, Box 114)
    - Belt from Fargo, undated (Folder 2, Box 114)
    - Cloth bag from Fargo, undated (Folder 4, Box 110)
    - Fargo Gaff Gauge, undated (Folder 4, Box 114)
    - Hat Labeled Fargo, undated (Folder 5, Box 114)
    - T-shirt labeled Fargo, undated (Folder 6, Box 114)
    - 5 drink stirrers labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 1, Box 115)
    - 15 spoons and thermometers from Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 2, Box 115)
    - Apron from Charles D. Davies, General Contractor, undated (Folder 3, Box 115)
    - Bank Pouch from Sherman Furniture, undated (Folder 4, Box 115)
    - Cigarette holder labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 5, Box 115)
    - Deck of Cards from Dutchess Bank, undated (Folder 6, Box 115)
    - Deck of cards labeled with local Poughkeepsie businesses, undated (Folder 7, Box 115)
    - DeLaval deck of cards in case, undated (Folder 8, Box 115)
    - KEM set of playing cards, undated (Folder 10, Box 115)
    - Dominos set from Reichardt's, undated (Folder 9, Box 115)
    - Paint Sample - #409 Red Mortar, undated (Folder 11, Box 115)
    - Pant Sample - Dutchess Manufacturing, undated (Folder 12, Box 115)
    - Large tin that contained Fairview Sausages from Knauss Brothers, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Box 116)
    - Wooden crate from Fitchett Bros. Dairy, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 117)
    - Wooden crate from Chester Club Beverages, Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 118)
    - Wooded bottle crate from F.R. Gillmann, Jr., Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Folder 1, Box 119)
    - Large box that contained Smith Brothers Menthol Medicated Cough Drops, undated (Folder 1, Box 120)
    - Large round heavy metal object with unknown purpose, undated (Folder 1, Box 121)
- 7. Graphic Materials, 1847 - 1987; 7; Boxes: 122 - 127
  Series contains photos from 300th Anniversary Parade, Dutchess County Historical Society Photos, Education, Luckey, Platt and Company, The Stereoscopic Society, and Miscellany
  - Subseries 7.1: 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987; 7.1; Box: 122
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 1, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 2, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 3, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 4, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 5, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 6, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 7, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 8, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 9, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 10, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 11, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 12, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 13, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 14, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 15, Box 122)
    - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 16, Box 122)